lontology Labs, LLC Quick Investor Packet

Thank you for taking the time to review this quick investor packet. The goal of this packet is to introduce you to the company, the product, and the team. As your interest in our company grows, we will be available to answer all of your questions regarding company finances, timelines, challenges, and successes.

In this packet, you will find the following information:

Iontology Labs, LLC Business Overview	2
Executive Summary	2
Objectives	2
Differentiators	2
Risks	2
Testing Panel	2
Funding Request	2
lontology Labs Entry/Exit Plans	3
Introduction	3
Entry Plan	3
Exit Plan	3
Iontology Scientific Team	4
Christina Resuello, M.Sc., MT	4
Yadi Stewart, MT (ASCP, AAB)	7

sales@iontology.net

lontology Labs, LLC 9250 Glades Rd #106 Boca Raton, FL 33434 (302) 670-7704

Working together to make it all work together

Iontology Labs, LLC Business Overview

I. Executive Summary

lontology Lab, LLC, is comprised of licensed medical technologists, mechanical engineers, experienced sales and marketing representatives, and information technologists. Our business will be formed as a Limited Liability Corporation, registered in Florida. Poised for rapid growth in the **clinical diagnostic** and **physician wellness testing industry**, lontology will expand into **whole health assessments**. The business seeks funding to take advantage of a window of opportunity for introducing this new laboratory into an evolving marketplace.

II. Objectives

The objectives of lontology are simple: provide life-enhancing molecular testing and pledge incredible customer support. As these objectives are met, lontology will become and remain profitable.

III. Differentiators

Becoming a startup is easy; becoming successful is tricky. The medical field has numerous certifications and qualifications testing, and with regard to Laboratory Testing, lontology has them covered. In addition, our team has written the protocols for other laboratories and successfully opened other laboratories without incident from credentialing agencies, something extremely rare in this field.

IV. Risks

As in any startup, there are risks. Our risks include inability to secure funding. Entry into this field requires at least 5 years of experience after education, and our team has it. Not just anyone can open a lab, but our team regularly does.

V. Testing Panel

Our initial testing platform will include **blood chemistry** and **drug testing**, including **medicinal marijuana testing**. Rapid growth within the first year will allow expansion into **cancer genetic markers screening** (Pharmacogenomics) and **molecular diagnostics** (LC/MS). As growth continues, we will assess other markets such as **infectious disease testing**, **forensics**, and **clinical trial testing** using the same methodology.

VI. Funding Request

lontology requests short-term debt funding of \$200,000 for initial laboratory start-up costs, equipment, and personnel. Majority of funds to be applied to sales and marketing, along with initial application fees and start-up supplies. The duration for initial AHCA application is 2-3 weeks, followed by COLA accreditation within the following 4-6 weeks. We will be able to begin to accept test samples 6 weeks after initial funding. Distributions from insurance companies are typically under 4 months once credentialed.

Iontology Labs Entry/Exit Plans

Introduction

lontology Labs, LLC, is comprised of a team of experts in clinical research laboratory setup and operation, seeks investment money into their minority women owned small business. This money, if accepted by lontology Labs, will be used to fund a Small Business Loan, which will then be used to obtain laboratory equipment, including a <u>Liquid Chromatography</u> / <u>Mass Spectrometry</u> (LC/MS) machine.

The LC/MS instrument is used to look at the specimen and determine basic blood work of a patient, if the sample is cancerous, or to aid the physician in treating for substance abuse. As we grow, we plan on enhancing our panel of tests available. Market predictions are that laboratories using the LC/MS equipment will account for \$7.3Billion global revenue by 2022.

In fact, this area is poised for heavy expansion, consolidation, and growth. One peer <u>laboratory</u> recently raised over \$2Million, just to handle marijuana testing (one of our initial tests). We are NOT seeking \$2Million, nor seeking their scale, yet. (They test states on the West Coast of the USA).

Our focus will start with the South Florida (Dade/Broward/Palm Beach) areas, and quickly expanding north, encompassing the entire state. We have a trained and dedicated sales force ready to handle the state.

By our best guess, nearly 3% of the medical facilities have adequate partnerships with laboratories. This means that result Turn-Around-Time (TAT) is higher than desired, requiring the operating labs to work more hours. This is a great opportunity for <u>students</u> who see this as a redefined, <u>stable industry</u> to work in as there is plenty of work.

Entry Plan

All of this positive energy makes it a great area for you to invest in. We are seeking one positive investor of \$75,000. This money will then be used to fund a Small Business loan, increasing its value to \$250,000; where we will then obtain our critical equipment, pay our startup crew, and obtain mandated licenses. We will have about 4 months of runway while we await receipt of the insurance payments; which usually takes 2-3 months.

Exit Plan

To show our appreciation to the investor, we are offering a monthly \$2,500 dividend check AFTER we are receiving insurance payments (approx 3 months). After 30 months, the investor will gracefully allow us to recapitalize our company by buying out our investor at 2x the initial entry price, a value of \$150,000. During the investment period, the investor will hold no equity or controlling interest in lontology Labs; but will be encouraged to keep us from going astray. This will provide a 3x ROI in 3 years with minimal risk.

Iontology Scientific Team

9612 Tavernier Dr., Boca Raton, FI 33496·302.670.7704·iontologyconsulting@gmail.com

Christina Resuello, M.Sc., MT

Summary

Experienced laboratory scientist and supervisor with strengths in laboratory management, program management, instrument analysis, analytical method development, DMPK, organic and inorganic laboratory methods, and forensic drug screening. Florida license SU 46379 (Clinical Chemistry Supervisor).

Experience

October 2016 – Present Iontology Consulting, LLC

Boca Raton, FI

Owner

Consultant for start-up laboratories, specializing in toxicology. Develop and validate methodology. Experienced with multiple LCMS platforms, including AB Sciex, Shimadzu, Waters TQD, Thermofisher LTQ/Orbitrap

June 2015 - Present

Lab Geeks, LLC/TLS

Deerfield Beach, FI

Technical Supervisor/General Supervisor LCMS, Toxicology

- Oversee daily duties for toxicology laboratory and start up laboratories under Total Lab Solutions management company
- Develop and validate analytical methods for testing panels (pain management, synthetics)

April 2014 – Present

First Choice Laboratory

Ft Lauderdale, Fl

Technical Supervisor, LCMS

- Provide oversight to LCMS data review technologists
- Develop and validate analytical methods for testing panels (opiates, benzodiazepines, barbiturates, illicits, SSRI)

November 2012 – March 2014 American Registry of Pathology

Dover, DE

Analytical Toxicologist II

- Confirmation scientist for military based DOD certified drug screening laboratory
- Develop and validate analytical methods for designer cathinones and synthetic cannabinoid testing

June 2011 – November 2012

SPI Pharma

Lewes, DE

Analytical Development Supervisor

- Manage daily instrumental laboratory operations
- Stability program manager
- Method validation program manager

December 2010 – June

DuPont

Newark, DE

2011

Laboratory Technician (Contract)

Analysis of pesticides for crop protection

June 2000-July 2010

AstraZeneca Pharmaceuticals

Wilmington, DE

Senior Associate Scientist

- Metabolite identification for drug research and candidate selection
- Formulation studies for in vivo PK
- Characterization of physical properties (ie/pKa, stability, protein binding, LogD)

Education

May 2008

Lehigh University

Bethlehem, PA

Master of Science, Pharmaceutical Chemistry

 Thesis: Identification of Artifacts in Cyanide Trapping of Reactive Intermediates in N-methyl Piperazine Analogs

May 1999

University of Delaware

Newark, DE

Bachelor of Arts, Biology

Certifications and Awards

Medical Technologist, AAB, Clinical Chemistry

Lean Six Sigma, Green Belt (DEMEP)

Certificate BioOrganic Principles (Lehigh University)

Business Certificates: Management, Marketing, Worker Safety, Human Resources

Extreme Team Award for significant contribution to supporting progression of lead candidate drug (AstraZeneca)

Excellence in Science Award for work contributing to development of GSH Trapping Assay (AstraZeneca)

Excellence in Science Award for work contributing to Integration of In-Silico Methods in Aqueous Formulation Design and Biopharmaceutical Assessment (AstraZeneca)

Extra Mile Award for contribution to formulation support (AstraZeneca)

Presentations/Publications

- 1. Contribution of Artifacts to N-methylated piperazine cyanide-adduct formation in vitro from N-alkyl piperazine analogs (Drug Metabolism and Disposition, 2013)
- 2. Evaluation of LC/MS Methods in Orbitrap, QTrap 4000, and QTOF Premier Mass Spectrometers to Screen and Identify GSH Adducts (Shanghai, 2008)
- 3. Integration of In silico Methods in Aqueous Formulation Design and Biopharmaceutical Assessment (AAPS, 2008)

Yadi Stewart, MT (ASCP, AAB)

Greater South Florida Area | yadistewart@gmail.com | 954-684-0615

Senior Medical Technologist | Technical Laboratory Manager | Toxicology | Pharmacogenomics | Chief Compliance Officer

Dynamic and experienced laboratory consultant in toxicology with proven record of ensuring maximum productivity through implementation of effective leadership among the members of team. Committed to constantly enhancing abilities with forward-thinking objectives that provide positive contributions to healthcare field and organizations. Expertise in preparing laboratories for COLA supervision, and passing consistently with scores over 97%. Proficient in CAP surveys and ensuring compliance for State of Florida, Pennsylvania, and with API agency. Currently pursuing Supervisor's License, expected to be obtained in 2017. Bilingual in Spanish and English. Notable accomplishments include: serving as first student accepted to externship at Cleveland Clinic in 11 years due to 4.0 GPA. Three degrees. Last one in Forensics, being able to apply this specialty to any kind of testing.

Core Skills, Knowledge, & Certifications

Team Management | Clinical Knowledge | Mentoring & Coaching | Staff Training | Data Entry | File Management | Word Processing | Organizational & Interpersonal Skills | Soft | Millennium | Paracelsus | Team Viewer (Remote review for LC/MS)

Certifications:

Medical Technologist (August 2016 to August 2018)

Generalist (licensed in 9 disciplines). Expert in Hematology Technologist, Immunohematology Technologist, Microbiology Technologist, Serology Technologist, Clinical Chemistry Technologist, Molecular Technologist.

Certification in Luminex 2D6 and 2C19

Professional Experience

Chief Compliance Officer |Lab Geeks & Total Lab Solutions October 2017-Present

Leading scientist for start up laboratories as managed by Total Lab Solutions. Validate and generate validation summaries for LCMS and screening instrumentation for Lab Geeks. Lead in the inspection process by preparing documentation and providing answers to COLA inspector questions. Assist in the development of quality assurance and control process. Provide regulatory guidance per COLA guidelines necessary for implementation for continued process improvements.

Technical Laboratory Consultant | Ziolo Consulting, LLC, West Palm Beach, FL April 2016-September 2016

Toxicology, Pharmacogenomics, LC/MS/MS, Generalist (5 Disciplines)

Direct technical and scientific procedures including: test methodology, verifying procedures for testing performed and establishing the laboratory's performance criteria, including accuracy and precision of each test and test system. Establish quality control program appropriate for the testing performed with acceptable levels of analytic performance, and ensuring such levels are maintained throughout testing process. Resolve technical problems and ensure corrective actions are taken whenever test systems

deviate from laboratory's established performance specifications. Direct corrective actions and ensure functioning of test systems. Identify training needs and in-service training of personnel, including competency and performance evaluations.

Laboratory Manager |Elite Labs LLC, Pompano Beach, FL Oct. 2014-April 2016

Toxicology, Pharmacogenomics, Chemistry, Urinalysis

Directed techniques, followed and wrote SOPs, including safety procedures dealing with biohazards waste, and sterile environment. Coordinated all activities associated with the lab. Ensured that training levels were maintained for Lab Technologists, Lab Technicians, Lab Assistants, and Techs in charge of the samples. Ensured required scientific equipment, instrumentation, and computer systems and compliance with valid licensure. Provided financial advice for the department and ensured that expense budgets were met (or maintained in line with revenue). Reported to next level manager and Study Directors regarding study status, technical problems and other issues which impact the lab and the patient care. Completed performance reviews equitably and on time; conducted regular one-on-one discussions with employees; ensured development plans were in place for all key employees; interviewed and hired job candidates.

• <u>Key Results:</u> Validated the FDA approved genetic markers 2D6 and 2C19.Personalized treatment through genetics. Collaborated with different Toxicology Laboratory, and the validation of two genetic markers, 2D6 and 2C19.

Senior Medical Technologist II Generalist | Memorial Healthcare System, Hollywood, FL 2011-2014

Served as Medical Technologist for Pembroke Hospital, West Hospital, and Urgent Care Center. Ensured lab was in compliance with JCAHO standards. Routinely performed Quality Control and Calibration Procedures on equipment to ensure the highest level of patient safety. Trained new staff as the specific procedures of laboratory. Focus areas included:

Hematology, Sysmex 5000, Sysmex 4000, Sysmex 2000, Urinalysis, Advantis, Chemistry, Vitros 600, Vitros 350, Cobas 6000, Elicys, Coagulation, Sysmex 1500, Sysmex 600, Blood Bank

Medical Technologist II |Trident Laboratories Inc. Hollywood, FL, 2012-2013

Toxicology, Chemistry, Urinalysis

Analyzed samples of urine to determine chemical content, cell count, and drug levels. Prepared samples for examination, using automated equipment and specialized Calibration and Proper QC of the equipment. Followed COLA standards; regularly assisted with surveys. Sampled for street and therapeutic drugs. Used Beckman AU480 and ELISA.

Additional Relevant Experience

Medical Technologist Microbiology Assistant (2011-2012)

Generalist, Coral Springs Medical Center, Coral Springs, FL (2011)

Externship, Cleveland Clinic of Florida, Weston, FL (2010)

Externship, Coral Springs Medical Center, Coral Springs, FL (2010)

Office Manager/Nurse Assistant, Neurological Pain Management, Lauderhill, FL (2003-2005)

Certified Nursing Assistant, Covenant Village of Florida, City of Sunrise, FL (2002-2003)

Education & Training

Bachelor of Science in Forensic Science Investigation, Keiser University, Fort Lauderdale, FL Associate of Science in Medical Laboratory Technician, Keiser University, Fort Lauderdale, FL Associate of Arts in Nursing, Broward Community College, Davie, FL

Processing Laboratory Supervisor License ASCP, AAB, AMT Member of Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society

sales@iontology.net

lontology Labs, LLC 9250 Glades Rd #106 Boca Raton, FL 33434 (302) 670-7704 Working together to make it all work together